got an anniversary coming up which I'm
looking forward to I got to get my wife
something
good oh hey you want to go in on
something we can do that this is from me
and three women from
Utah there you
go
yeah I took her bungee jumping last year
that's what she really wanted to do
bungee jumping and uh anybody done it
anybody done bungee jumping any have you
done it really good for you good for you
you Brave good for you how far did you
bunge
you you you don't even know I think
that'd be the first thing I'd find
out how far to the ground MH and how far
is a
rope
okay got to just checked into it a
little bit more I think but well good
for you what did you jump off of what
was it Tower oh tea Tower yeah that
sounds like they've got all their
insurance paperwork up
today minimalist space were you afraid
when you did it yeah good for you that's
brains that's that's we went we went
from a hot air balloon you ever hear of
anything like that yeah well here's
what's going to happen we're going to go
up in the Mounds great day we're going
to go up in the mountains up in the air
in a hot air balloon 250 ft she's going
to bungee from the balloon 220 ft we get
in the basket on the way up this guy
leans over me he said listen sometimes
people are afraid to go she don't go on
a count of three you think you can push
her yes
yeah I mean don't get me wrong I love my
wife and everything but there isn't a
married guy in this room that wouldn't
just like to one
time oh it is therapeutic everything
comes I push it too I couldn't help it
go have a good
time I love
you I don't mean to be like that and
don't get me wrong man I love my wife
I'm crazy about that woman but I just
get so do aggravated matters
sometimes we argue gez Almighty we argue
we argue over the stupidest littlest
teeniest Tinus couldn't possibly
matter I can't load a dishwasher
wrong it's not like I'm taping the
dishes to the outside of the machine and
standing there like
a it's the first
dish just move it around until you're
happy but that that's what you fight
about the big stuff big stuff you lean
on each other and it's really really
great but the little little little
little
little we had an argument one time half
an hour whether or not a dolphin is a
fish 30 minutes whether or not a do I
mean I know that a dolphin's not a
fish
[Applause]
now would you at least admit that it
lives a fish
lifestyle
got an argument in the carco man that is
the worst place to have an argument
you're
stuck big argument about my driving you
know and she's got a little room to
gripe I'll give her that cuz I'm a boob
in the car I don't know you ever been
driving around and can't see an address
or something that you're looking for so
you turn the radio down like that'll
help I can't see anything with this
music in my
eye and this clear piece of glass has
got to
go
how old is my car seriously I know I
know I right
[Applause]
yeah we went for a we went for a
relaxing Drive in the mountains not too
long ago and as we're headed up into the
mountains there's this big sign on the
side of the road just splashing scared
watch for Falling
Rock and I did that and uh hit a guy on
a
bike oh that was off I was like all
right we're in the Rock
Zone everybody keep a sharp
eye what the heck was
[Music]
that all right all right everybody
listen up when the police get
here that guy was hit by a
rock we
off so I don't know I don't know I don't
know whether I'm a good driver or a bad
driver but I do know that one steering
wheel means one driver okay shush
shush not to hear my wife tell it you
know Phil even a fighter pilot has a
wingman well yeah but I don't think he
warns the pilot by screaming
[Applause]
out well I get nervous I don't know what
to say well how about
car
I don't even understand why she gets so
nervous it doesn't this is a woman that
has jumped from a perfectly good
airplane strapped to a little backpack
full of nylon she didn't think a thing
of that but a car in a parking lot backs
up slowly towards
AR I'm tell man she she does some things
like that that just aggravate the death
out ofy and then she does some things
that aggravate me but I love her because
of them I can't figure that out that's
Love's little
twist it's like biting a hang nail over
and over again even though you know it
hurts
[Music]
ow
oh and now it's bleeding all
right
mhm she's got the bedroom clock set 20
minutes fast so that we can get an extra
20 minutes of
sleep yeah
figure that out now every day wake up 20
minutes early just to find out it's not
that late
yet she has her own ridiculous rational
to no no no now we can go back to
sleep I was
sleeping I didn't need to wake up to do
it I have no idea what time it is in my
house we have 12:00 none set on the
proper time you could be on one side of
my house 5 to one toward the middle it's
125 close the other side is 10 to2
you're like for heaven's sakes how big
is this
house I was just in the bathroom a half
an hour from now how is that
[Applause]
possible work day is almost over you
guys really have been terrific I really
appreciate coming out this is the
funnest part of my day it's hard to be
gone so much I miss my wife quite a lot
hard to be gone I called her today
though talked to her on the phone for a
little bit told her that I loved her cu
cuz uh she won't hang up the phone
unless I
do which is fine man if you love
somebody for heaven's sakes tell them
tell them tell them all the time why
keep it in but it's crafty over the
phone because then you become so
conditioned doesn't matter who you're
talking
to yeah I'd like a large pepperoni uhhuh
30 minutes fantastic I love
you you feel like an idiot better get a
pizza in 5 minutes
Pepperoni's in a hard
shape new Facebook friend it's
wonderful but I do love that lady dog on
it then you want to show them man you
want to show them that you love them and
you cherish you know but I flub it up
somewhere along the way you know I goof
it up here's what happened recently I
take my wife out to dinner we go to this
fanc restaurant's packed we have to wait
for a table so we're in the bar having a
drink and I got to go to the bathroom so
I get up I go to the bathroom I come
back there's some guy hitting on my my
wife now my
dude she's with
me but he's not buying
it
so I Spit on
her